<?xml version="1.0"?>
<pictures>
	<picture>
		<id>SS1</id>
		<name>Starry Night</name>
		<author>Van Gogh</author>
		<description>The Starry Night is an oil on canvas by the Dutch post-impressionist painter Vincent van Gogh.
Painted in June, 1889, it depicts the view from the east-facing window of his asylum room at Saint-Remy-de-Provence, just before sunrise, with the addition of an idealized village.
It is regarded as among Van Gogh's finest works, and one of the most recognized monuments in the history of Western culture.</description>
	</picture>
	<picture>
		<id>SS3</id>
		<name>Arrangement in Grey and Black</name>
		<author>Whistler</author>
		<description>Arrangement in Grey and Black No.1, famous under its colloquial name Whistler's Mother, is a painting in oils on canvas created by the American-born painter James McNeill Whistler in 1871.
The painting is 56.81 by 63.94 inches, displayed in a frame of Whistler's own design.
It is one of the most famous works by an American artist outside the United States. It has been variously described as an American icon and a Victorian Mona Lisa.</description>
	</picture>
	<picture>
		<id>SS5</id>
		<name>The Kiss</name>
		<author>Klimt</author>
		<description>The Kiss (Lovers) was painted by the Austrian Symbolist painter Gustav Klimt between 1908 and 1909, the highpoint of his "Golden Period", when he painted a number of works in a similar gilded style.
The work is composed of oil paint with applied layers of gold leaf, an aspect that gives it its strikingly modern, yet evocative appearance.
It is a symbol of Vienna Jugendstil—Viennese Art Nouveau—and is considered Klimt's most popular work.</description>
	</picture>
	<picture>
		<id>SS7</id>
		<name>The Son of Man</name>
		<author>Magritte</author>
		<description>The Son of Man is a 1964 painting by the Belgian surrealist painter Rene Magritte.
Magritte painted it as a self-portrait. The painting consists of a man in an overcoat and a bowler hat standing in front of a low wall, beyond which is the sea and a cloudy sky. The man's face is largely obscured by a hovering green apple.
The Son of Man resembles The Great War on Façades, another Magritte painting featuring similar imagery. Both feature a person standing in front of a wall overlooking the sea.</description>
	</picture>
	<picture>
		<id>SS6</id>
		<name>Guernica</name>
		<author>Picasso</author>
		<description>Guernica is a mural-sized oil painting on canvas by Spanish artist Pablo Picasso completed by June 1937. The painting, which uses a palette of gray, black, and white, is known as one of the most moving and powerful anti-war paintings in history.
The painting is believed to be a response to the bombing of Guernica, a Basque Country village in northern Spain, by German and Italian warplanes at the request of the Spanish Nationalists.
Upon completion, Guernica was displayed around the world in a brief tour, becoming famous and widely acclaimed, and believed to have helped bring worldwide attention to the Spanish Civil War.</description>
	</picture>
	<picture>
		<id>SS9</id>
		<name>The Scream</name>
		<author>Munch</author>
		<description>The Scream is the popular name given to each of four versions of a composition, created as both paintings and pastels, by the Expressionist artist Edvard Munch between 1893 and 1910.
The Scream of Nature is the title Munch gave to these works, all of which show a figure with an agonized expression against a landscape with a tumultuous orange sky. Arthur Lubow has described The Scream as an icon of modern art, a Mona Lisa for our time.
Edvard Munch created the four versions in various media.</description>
	</picture>
</pictures>